Skip to content
Personal Open source Business Explore
Sign upSign inPricingBlogSupport
This repository
Search
 Watch 1  Star 0  Fork 159 Bakaba/NadekoBot
forked from Kwoth/NadekoBot
 Code  Pull requests 0  Pulse  Graphs
Branch: master Find file Copy pathNadekoBot/NadekoBot/bin/Debug/data/questions.json
11e0094  on May 10
@Bakaba Bakaba Removed the last coma.
2 contributors @Bakaba @Kwoth
RawBlameHistory     3783 lines (3782 sloc)  105 KB
[
  {
    "Category": "Anime",
    "Question": " In the anime 'Shingetsutan Tsukihime', how many beast Nrvnqsr(Nero) Chaos's body contain?",
    "Answer": "666"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Anime",
    "Question": " In the anime 'Rozen Maiden', Souseiseki (Twin sister of Suiseiseki) have minnow eyes, one green and one red. Which eye is red?",
    "Answer": "Left"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Anime",
    "Question": " In the anime 'Vision of Escaflowne', what is the name of the male protagonist?",
    "Answer": "Van Fanel"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Anime",
    "Question": " In the anime 'Kyoukai no Kanata', what is the name of the main character?",
	"Answer": "Akihito Kanbara"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Anime",
    "Question": " What is the name of the most recent 'Tenchi Muyo' series?",
    "Answer": "Shin Tenchi Muyo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Arts",
    "Question": " How is also called an artists workshop or studio?",
    "Answer": "Atelier"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Arts",
    "Question": " What Spaniard designed the five-story horse in Chicago's Daley Plaza?",
    "Answer": "Pablo Picasso"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Arts",
    "Question": " What late female painter's art, drawn from desert scenes fueled calendar sales?",
    "Answer": "Georgia O'Keeffe"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Arts",
    "Question": " In what field of study would you find 'flying buttresses'?",
    "Answer": "Architecture"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " True of false: The dolphin have to stop physically to sleep.",
    "Answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What's the fastest man can run - 18, 28 or 38 miles per hour?",
    "Answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How often (in years) the female condor lays a egg?",
    "Answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How far (in miles) the smell of a skunk can be detected by a human?",
    "Answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " According to tradition, which animals desert a sinking ship?",
    "Answer": "Rats"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many tentacles does an octopus have?",
    "Answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many legs does a spider have?",
    "Answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " About how fast can a dragonfly fly; 10, 20, 30 or 40 miles per hour?",
    "Answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " A herb or drug described as 'haemostatic' performs which effect?",
    "Answer": "Stops bleeding"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The biggest electric ray, the Atlantic torpedo ray, can weigh how many pounds?",
    "Answer": "200"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Bull giraffes forage higher or lower in trees than cow giraffes?",
    "Answer": "Higher"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How is called a wild ox?",
    "Answer": "Bison"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What part of the human body holds the head to shoulders?",
    "Answer": "Neck"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What Arizona snake is not poisonous, but can vibrate its tail like a rattlesnake?",
    "Answer": "Gopher snake"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " An average adult raccoon weighs how many pounds?",
    "Answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which complex alcohol is a constituent of all animal fats and oils?",
    "Answer": "Cholesterol"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What a dolphin can remember specifically better than a human?",
    "Answer": "Tone"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What a terrapin is a type of?",
    "Answer": "Turtle"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How is called a bone specialist?",
    "Answer": "Osteopath"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which takes more muscles to do, frowning or smiling?",
    "Answer": "Frowning"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How much of the world's population is left-handed, 5 percent, 10 percent, 15 percent or 20 percent?",
    "Answer": "10 percent"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many times a day does an average adult person laugh, 10 times, 15 times, 20 times or 25 times?",
    "Answer": "15 times"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What insect is known for being a carrier of malaria, encephalitis, yellow fever and dengue fever?",
    "Answer": "Mosquitos"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What continent is the only one on Earth that has no reptiles or snakes?",
    "Answer": "Antarctica"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What breed of dog bites more humans than any other breed?",
    "Answer": "German Shepherds"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " True or false: Adolescent male crickets can chirp.",
    "Answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The blood of mammals is red. What color is a lobster's blood?",
    "Answer": "Blue"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The word 'ass' refers to several hoofed mammals of the genus Equus, including which one?",
    "Answer": "Onager"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " A garter snake can give birth to how many babies?",
    "Answer": "85"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal can swim for a 1/2 mile without resting, and can tread water for 3 days straight?",
    "Answer": "Rat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How far can a skunk spray: 5, 10 or 15 feet?",
    "Answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the most famous america reindeer?",
    "Answer": "Caribou"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What an animal need to have to be a fish?",
    "Answer": "Gills"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal is the only one to be born with horns?",
    "Answer": "Giraffe"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What bird have a natural habitat inaccessible and of little use to man?",
    "Answer": "Flamingo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " With red meat, what monkeys will not eat?",
    "Answer": "Butter"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " In which country a peak in wildlife population occurs in a cycle of about 9 years?",
    "Answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal, with short-tailed shrews, sleep only two hours a day?",
    "Answer": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": "Anthocyanins are compounds which produce what?",
    "Answer": "Colors"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Boxer dogs will stand on his hind legs and bat at his opponent, appearing to 'box' with what?",
    "Answer": "Front paws"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Australia exports how many crocodile skins a year?",
    "Answer": "5000"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Camels in captivity can live up to how many years?",
    "Answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal feel safest when they are crowded together, about hundreds in a group?",
    "Answer": "Flamingo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What dog have the best eyesight of any breed?",
    "Answer": "Greyhound"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Javelina is more sensitive to cold or heat?",
    "Answer": "Cold"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal have a brain about six times heavier than a human?",
    "Answer": "Sperm whale"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Milk snakes lay about how many eggs?",
    "Answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The leech have how many brains?",
    "Answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Elephants, lions, and camels roamed what place 12,000 years ago?",
    "Answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " In which country pink elephants can be found?",
    "Answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal herd post their own sentries, which can alert the rest of the herd in case of danger?",
    "Answer": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": "What animal may travel about 25,000 miles in all in a single year on migrations?",
    "Answer": "Bird"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How is called a camel with two hump?",
    "Answer": "Bactrian"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Baby beavers are called kits or?",
    "Answer": "Kittens"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Because its tongue is too short for its beak, what animal must juggle its food before swallowing it?",
    "Answer": "Toucan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What giant Pacific animal can fit its entire body through an opening no bigger than the size of its beak?",
    "Answer": "Octopus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal that has been neutered is known as a 'wether'?",
    "Answer": "Goat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " In one night, a mole can dig a tunnel to how much feet: 50, 100, 300 or 500?",
    "Answer": "300"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How is called a young pigeon that has not yet flown?",
    "Answer": "Squab"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What all porcupines float in?",
    "Answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The average person has a vocabulary of: 4,000, 5,000 or 6,000 words?",
    "Answer": "5,000"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which part of the human body accounts for one quarter of the bones the body contains?",
    "Answer": "Feet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What does a person with hexidectylism have?",
    "Answer": "Six fingers or six toes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which of the big, jungle cats is the only cat to be social rather than solitary?",
    "Answer": "The lion"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What type of nucleic acid carries hereditary information from generation to generation?",
    "Answer": "Deoxyribonucleic acid"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the body's largest internal organ?",
    "Answer": "Small intestine"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " 'Daffodils' belong to which genus of bulb?",
    "Answer": "Narcissus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many bones does a shark have?",
    "Answer": "Zero"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which do mosquitos prefer, brunettes or blonds?",
    "Answer": "Blonds"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which do mosquitos prefer, children or adults?",
    "Answer": "Children"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What part of the mosquito does citronella bother the most?",
    "Answer": "Their feet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Herbivorous means only plants are eaten for food. What word means anything is eaten for food?",
    "Answer": "Omnivorous"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " A zebra is which: black with white stripes or white with black stripes?",
    "Answer": "White with black stripes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Cats are the only domestic animals that walk directly on their what?",
    "Answer": "Claws"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal smell 44 times better than humans?",
    "Answer": "Sheepdog"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " At least how many muscles have a bird wing?",
    "Answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How are called animals that once existed and exist no more?",
    "Answer": "Extinct"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What bird spread their wings, clack bills, and shake heads in a ritual dance?",
    "Answer": "Albatros"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " When young abalones feed on red seaweed, their shells turn to what color?",
    "Answer": "Red"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What a camel's humps made up of?",
    "Answer": "Fat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What animal produces the loudest sound of any animal on Earth?",
    "Answer": "The blue whale"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which animal, cat or dog, has the most vocal sounds?",
    "Answer": "Cats"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What gossamer-winged insect is the fastest flying of all the insects?",
    "Answer": "Dragonflies"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many worker bees would have to spend their lifetime to produce 1 teaspoon of honey?",
    "Answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the world's largest living bird?",
    "Answer": "Ostrich"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The blood of mammals is red. What color is insect's blood?",
    "Answer": "Yellow"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What's an organism made from the genetic material of another commonly called?",
    "Answer": "Clone"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What bird in the heron family is named for the long feathers, or 'aigrettes', grown by the male during mating season?",
    "Answer": "Egret"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Who is the only bird that can fly backwards?",
    "Answer": "Hummingbird"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Who is the only mammal that can fly?",
    "Answer": "Bat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What does the male Emperor Penguine balance atop his feet for two months while its mate feeds?",
    "Answer": "Egg"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the only mammal that can fly, and not simply glide?",
    "Answer": "Bat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which ostrish organ is bigger: eye or brain?",
    "Answer": "Eye"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many eyelids does a camel's eye have?",
    "Answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " True or false: Snakes are immune to their own poison.",
    "Answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which insect is responsible for the most human deaths world-wide?",
    "Answer": "Mosquito"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " True or false: The bones of a pidgeon weigh less than it's feathers.",
    "Answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What bird is the only bird in the world that can fly backwards?",
    "Answer": "The hummingbird"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the underside of a horse's hoove called?",
    "Answer": "Frog"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the most common mammal in the United States?",
    "Answer": "The mouse"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " The poison-arrow frog has enough poison to kill how many people; 10, 500, 1,200 or 2,200?",
    "Answer": "2,200"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Whose venom is more potent, a rattlesnake's or a female black widow spider's?",
    "Answer": "The female black widow spider's"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Which can last longer without water, a camel or a rat?",
    "Answer": "A rat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What is the world's largest mammal?",
    "Answer": "The blue whale"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " Of the approximately 2,600 different species of frogs, what is the only continent that they don't live on?",
    "Answer": "Antartica"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " How many bones are there in the adult human body?",
    "Answer": "206"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Biology",
    "Question": " What's defined as 'species not definitely located in the wild during the past 50 years'?",
    "Answer": "Endangered species"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": "In the game 'Moutain of Faith(Touhou Project)', what is the name of the boss of stage 3?",
    "Answer": "Nitori Kawashiro"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": "In the game 'Touhou Project', Alice Margatroid's first appearance is as a child. But in which Touhou?",
    "Answer": "Mystic Square"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": "In the game 'Touhou Project', how many different masks have Hata no Kokoro in total?",
    "Answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": "In the game 'Embodiment of Scarlet Devil(Touhou Project)', what is the name of Remilia Scarlet's young sister?",
	"Answer": "Flandre Scarlet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": " In the game 'Touhou Project', on what animals Suwako and Kanako are respectively based?",
	"Answer": "Frog and snake"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": "In the game 'Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney', what is the original name of Phoenix Wright?",
	"Answer": "Ryuuichi Naruhodou"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": " In the game 'Cluedo', what is the name of the only woman suspect who isn't married?",
    "Answer": "Miss Scarlett"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Games",
    "Question": " In a game of snooker, how many balls are used in addition to the cue ball?",
    "Answer": "Twenty-one"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the only man-made feature visible from space?",
    "Answer": "Great Wall of China"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What U.S. state adopted a cactus blossom as its state flower?",
    "Answer": "Arizona" 
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What's the first foreign country you'd reach by traveling due south from Detroit's City Airport?",
    "Answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What well-known ancient site in England is 1,500 years older then the Colosseum in Rome?",
    "Answer": "Stonehenge"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "Alphabetically speaking, which is the last of the 26 Irish counties?",
    "Answer": "Wicklow"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What continent boasts Angel Falls, the tallest in the world?",
    "Answer": "South America"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What's the name of the stately stone gate in the center of Berlin?",
    "Answer": "The Brandenburg Gate"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the national bird of New Zealand?",
    "Answer": "Kiwi"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " How tall is the Eiffel Tower; 196, 583, 721 or 984 feet?",
    "Answer": "984"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which animal are the Canary Islands named after?",
    "Answer": "Dog"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the lowest point on land in the world?",
    "Answer": "The Dead Sea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What African country is only 8 miles from Spain?",
    "Answer": "Morocco"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " America's country's first commercial oil well was located in what state?",
    "Answer": "Pennsylvania"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which of Michigan's 'Great Lakes' lies entirely inside the United States?",
    "Answer": "Lake Michigan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the most important inland waterway in North America?",
    "Answer": "The Great Lakes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Alberta's shield on the coat of arms, bears the cross of?",
    "Answer": "Saint George"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Name all of the 'Great Lakes' that surround Michigan.",
    "Answer": "Michigan, Huron, Erie and Superior"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which US state has 8 national park sites?",
    "Answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which is larger, the island of Manhattan in New York or Disney World in Orlando in Florida?",
    "Answer": "Disney World"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " How many deserts are in or extend into the United States?",
    "Answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which ocean is the smallest and shallowest?",
    "Answer": "Artic Ocean"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which ocean is saltier, the Pacific or the Atlantic?",
    "Answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What name was the city of St. Petersburg, Russia given in 1914 because Russian leaders thought it's name sounded too German?",
    "Answer": "Petrograd"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What name was the city of St. Petersburg, Russia given in 1924 to honor the founder of the Soviet Union?",
    "Answer": "Petrograd"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What desert Mongolia and China share?",
    "Answer": "Gobi"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What country's national flag is flown differently depending on if the country is at war or at peace?",
    "Answer": "Philippines"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the highest mountain range in the world?",
    "Answer": "The Himilayas"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What body of water does the river Danube empty into?",
    "Answer": "The Black Sea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What city is the oldest one in the United States?",
    "Answer": "St. Augustine"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " How many cities in the world boast populations in excess of 1 million people; over 50, 200, 300 or 400?",
    "Answer": "300"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the southern most capital city in the world?",
    "Answer": "Wellington"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the narrow sea between the Arabian Peninsula and Africa called?",
    "Answer": "The Red Sea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What former Middle Eastern tourist mecca has been reduced to rubble by civil war and terrorism?",
    "Answer": "Beirut"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What skyscraper shares New York state's nickname?",
    "Answer": "The Empire State Building"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the highest mountain in the world?",
    "Answer": "Mt. Everest"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the largest 'lake' in the world?",
    "Answer": "The Caspian Sea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the largest lake in North America?",
    "Answer": "Lake Superior"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Where is the Weddell Sea?",
    "Answer": "Antartica"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the highest waterfall in the world?",
    "Answer": "Angel Falls"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the longest river in the world?",
    "Answer": "The Nile"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What do Istanbul, Constantinople, and Byzantium have in common?",
    "Answer": "They are the same place"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the largest lake in Africa?",
    "Answer": "Lake Victoria"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the world's largest desert?",
    "Answer": "The Sahara"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What U.S. city is also called 'The Windy City'?",
    "Answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the highest mountain in Africa?",
    "Answer": "Mt. Kilimanjaro"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which well-known Russian city has seen it's name changed 3 times since it was founded in 1703 by Peter the Great?",
    "Answer": "St. Petersburg"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the Spanish name for the South American capital which means 'good air'?",
    "Answer": "Buenos Aires"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Ecuador?",
    "Answer": "Quito"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Somalia?",
    "Answer": "Mogadishu"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which country is the world's leading importer of iron ore?",
    "Answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What country's name is a Native American Indian word meaning 'Big Village'?",
    "Answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Over which waterfall does the most water flow over per year?",
    "Answer": "Niagara Falls"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Hungary?",
    "Answer": "Budapest"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What middle eastern state was founded in 1948?",
    "Answer": "Israel"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which large island is 3 times the size of Texas?",
    "Answer": "Greenland"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which county in Great Britain is the only one that has 2 coasts?",
    "Answer": "Devon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Rome was originally built on how many hills?",
    "Answer": "Seven"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What group of islands boasts the 'wettest spot on Earth' because of the rainfall there?",
    "Answer": "The Hawaiian Islands"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the world's smallest independant state.",
    "Answer": "Vatican City"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which state is the only one whose name has only one syllable?",
    "Answer": "Maine"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which sea lies along the western side of Holland (the Netherlands)?",
    "Answer": "North Sea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the largest island in the world?",
    "Answer": "Greenland"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which large, well-known Central American city is sinking at the rate of 6 to 8 inches per year?",
    "Answer": "Mexico City"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which one of Earth's oceans is mostly covered by solid ice, ice floes and icebergs?",
    "Answer": "Arctic Ocean"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " True or false: In Paraguay dueling is still legal as long as both parties are registered blood donors.",
    "Answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which country is also a continent?",
    "Answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which is the only state that grows coffee?",
    "Answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What city in the world was the first one to reach the population of 1 million people?",
    "Answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " True or false: Michigan's Great Lakes are the largest group of freshwater lakes in the world.",
    "Answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " In area, which city is larger, Los Angeles, California or Juneau, Alaska?",
    "Answer": "Juneau"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What country lies along the western side of Spain?",
    "Answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the most populous city in North America?",
    "Answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " In what city is the Smithsonian Institute?",
    "Answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " In which city is Red Square?",
    "Answer": "Moscow"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " In which city is the Coliseum located?",
    "Answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Into what body of water does the 'Danube River' flow?",
    "Answer": "Black sea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Linz, Austria is a leading port on which river?",
    "Answer": "Danube"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Madrid and Lisbon are both located near what river?",
    "Answer": "Tagus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the longest river in Asia?",
    "Answer": "Yangtze"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " On what island is the Blue Grotto?",
    "Answer": "Capri"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " On what peninsula are Spain and Portugal located?",
    "Answer": "The iberian peninsula"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " On which river is the Aswan High Dam?",
    "Answer": "Nile"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What canal connects Lake Ontario and Lake Erie?",
    "Answer": "Welland"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What city is the Christian Science Monitor based in?",
    "Answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What country formed the union of Tanganyika and Zanzibar?",
    "Answer": "Tanzania"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What English city does the Prime Meridian pass through?",
    "Answer": "Greenwich"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Andorra?",
    "Answer": "Andorra la Vella"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Angola?",
    "Answer": "Luanda"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Australia?",
    "Answer": "Canberra"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Bhutan?",
    "Answer": "Thimphu"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Colorado?",
    "Answer": "Denver"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Equatorial Guinea?",
    "Answer": "Malabo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Finland?",
    "Answer": "Helsinki"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Iraq?",
    "Answer": "Baghdad"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Ireland?",
    "Answer": "Dublin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Kuwait?",
    "Answer": "Kuwait City"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Monaco?",
    "Answer": "Monaco"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Niger?",
    "Answer": "Niamey"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Papua New Guinea?",
    "Answer": "Port Moresby"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Solomon Islands?",
    "Answer": "Honiara"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Switzerland?",
    "Answer": "Bern"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Tanzania?",
    "Answer": "Dar es Salaam"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Tonga?",
    "Answer": "Nuku'alofa"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Turkmenistan?",
    "Answer": "Ashkhabad"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital of Tuvalu?",
    "Answer": "Fanafuti"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the highest mountain in Canada?",
    "Answer": "Mt. Logan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the largest of the countries in Central America?",
    "Answer": "Nicaragua"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which Irish city is famous for its crystal?",
    "Answer": "Waterford"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which is the Earth's fourth largest continent?",
    "Answer": "South America"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which state is the 'Garden State'?",
    "Answer": "New Jersey"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which U.S. city is known as the 'Biggest Little City in the World'?",
    "Answer": "Reno"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which U.S. state borders a Canadian territory?",
    "Answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What is the capital city of Utah?",
    "Answer": "Salt Lake City"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What mountain range separates Europe from Asia?",
    "Answer": "Urals"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What U.S. state is known as The Land of 10,000 Lakes?",
    "Answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " In which city is Beacon Street?",
    "Answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " In which US city is the Sears tower?",
    "Answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which Central American country extends furthest north?",
    "Answer": "Belize"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " Which city is known as Motown?",
    "Answer": "Detroit"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What tropical U.S. state has chosen the yellow hibiscus as it's state flower?",
    "Answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": " What European country contains Transylvania, commonly considered to be the home of 'Count Dracula'?",
    "Answer": "Romania"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who did Cleopatra wed after frustrating marriages with her two younger brothers?",
    "Answer": "Marc Antony"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Whose signature on the USA's 'Declaration Of Independance' is legible from the farthest distance?",
    "Answer": "John Hancock's"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " 'Operation Desert Storm' took place in: 1989, 1991 or 1995?",
    "Answer": "1991"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What was the name of the B-29 bomber that dropped the Atomic Bomb on Nagasaki?",
    "Answer": "Bock's Car"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What form of ancient writing was finally deciphered with the help of a chunk of basalt known as the Rosetta Stone?",
    "Answer": "Hieroglyphics"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What country did the U.S. and Britain blame for the 1988 plane bombing over Scotland?",
    "Answer": "Libya"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " When was the Rosetta stone found?",
    "Answer": "1799"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Where are the great Walls of Babylon located in the modern day world?",
    "Answer": "Iraq"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What is the name of the Greek wine god?",
    "Answer": "Dionysus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What 2 countries fought the 'Hundred Years War'?",
    "Answer": "France and England"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the first 'elected' President of Russia?",
    "Answer": "Boris Yeltsin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In what year did Alaska become a state?",
    "Answer": "1959"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year did women win the right to vote in national elections in the U.S.?",
    "Answer": "1920"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who did the Roman Catholic Church admit was right 350 years ago to suggest Earth revolved around the sun?",
    "Answer": "Galileo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which president almost died during birth, when his mother was given an overdose of chloroform?",
    "Answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who warned in 1917: 'This is only a preliminary step toward a similar revolution everywhere'?",
    "Answer": "V.I. Lenin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What president was so unpopular that he almost didn't get his name on a dam?",
    "Answer": "Herbert Hoover"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In what year was the 'Magna Carta' signed?",
    "Answer": "1215"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In what city did Rosa Parks first take a stand against 'Jim Crow' laws by refusing to stand?",
    "Answer": "Montgomery"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which famous piece of artwork depcits the 'Battle of Hastings'?",
    "Answer": "Bayeux Tapestry"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What religion was founded by Lao-tzu?",
    "Answer": "Taoism"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What country did Hitler's troops invade, kicking off World War II?",
    "Answer": "Poland"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In ancient Egypt which animal was considered sacred?",
    "Answer": "Cat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What fort's 1814 bombardment inspired Francis Scott Key to pen the USA's anthem's lyrics?",
    "Answer": "Fort McHenry"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " To date, who has been the only American president to win non-consecutive terms to the White House?",
    "Answer": "President Grover Cleveland"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " 'The 900 Days' is a chronicle about what group's siege of Leningrad?",
    "Answer": "Nazi"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which god was a favourite of the Roman legions, who sacrificed a bull to him in secret rituals?",
    "Answer": "Mithras"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What is the name of the only U.S. President who was never married?",
    "Answer": "James Buchanan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In what ancient city did Alexander the Great die?",
    "Answer": "Babylon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the first director of Britain's National Theatre?",
    "Answer": "Laurence Olivier"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " True or false: French was never the official language of England.",
    "Answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " The ancient Egyptians used what substance as the earliest know contraceptive?",
    "Answer": "Crocodile dung"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year was the Republic of Israel established, 1933, 1948, 1957 or 1966?",
    "Answer": "1948"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the Greek goddess of victory?",
    "Answer": "Nike"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What country found wooden shoes to be no match for German jackboots in 1940?",
    "Answer": "The Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What city General Sherman burned in 1864?",
    "Answer": "Atlanta"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who ruled Rome when Christ was born?",
    "Answer": "Caesar Augustus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In what year of WW II did Russia declare war on Japan?",
    "Answer": "1945"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?",
    "Answer": "China"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What Roman city was founded in 753 BC?",
    "Answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What did Temujin change his name to?",
    "Answer": "Genghis Khan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Israel occupied the Golan Heights. Whose territory was it?",
    "Answer": "Syria"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What state's license plates began saying 'Famous Potatoes' in 1957?",
    "Answer": "Idaho's"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the first pilot to take off solo in New York and land in Paris?",
    "Answer": "Charles Lindbergh"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " How many buffalo/bison roamed North America in 1492 - 600,000, 6 million or 60 million?",
    "Answer": "60 million"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " American indians used beads as currency. What was it called?",
    "Answer": "Wampum"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What is the name of an american inventor and teacher of the deaf, most famous for his invention of the telephone?",
    "Answer": "Alexander Graham Bell"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What was the name of the B-29 that dropped the bomb on Hiroshima?",
    "Answer": "Enola Gay"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What industry, according to Melvin Belli, 'has conspired to catch you, hold you and kill you'?",
    "Answer": "Tobacco industry"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " How did Rasputin die, after being poisoned, shot, beaten, bound and thrown in the Neva River?",
    "Answer": "Drown"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who opined: 'Everybody has a right to pronounce foreign names as he chooses'?",
    "Answer": "Winston Churchill"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which military man was nicknamed 'The Little Corporal'?",
    "Answer": "Napoleon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What 15th-century prince is thought to have been the inspiration for the classic 'Dracula'?",
    "Answer": "Vlad the Impaler"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What British political party made Margaret Thatcher its first female leader?",
    "Answer": "The Conservative (Tory) Party"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What 'Little Boy' & 'Fat Man' were the first?",
    "Answer": "Atomic bombs"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " About which Prime Minister was it said 'He could never see a belt without hitting below it'?",
    "Answer": "Lloyd george"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " According to John Aubrey's Brief Lives , what card game did the English poet, Sir John Suckling, invent in 1630?",
    "Answer": "Cribbage"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What name did Mohammed A. Salameh use when he rented the van that carried the bomb that blew up the World Trade Center in New York City?",
    "Answer": "Mohammed A. Salameh"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What was the name of the battle in which Hannibal was defeated?",
    "Answer": "Zama"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What building did a wayward B-25 smack the 78th floor of in 1945?",
    "Answer": "The Empire State Building"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What war cost an average of one billion dollars a day?",
    "Answer": "The Persian Gulf War"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What Kenyan secret terrorist organization revolted against British colonists in 1952?",
    "Answer": "Mau Mau"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which people created the sundial?",
    "Answer": "The Egyptians"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What did Supreme Court nominee Douglas Ginsberg describe as a 'mistake' he made as a Harvard prof?",
    "Answer": "Smoking marijuana"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What assassin's low self-esteem is often attributed to his undiagnosed dyslexia?",
    "Answer": "Lee Harvey Oswald"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " How many aircraft carriers were in Pearl Harbor when the Japanese attack occurred?",
    "Answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who did Paris, the ruler of Troy, select as the most beautiful goddess?",
    "Answer": "Aphrodite"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " True or false: The Jordanian city, Amman, was once called Philadelphia.",
    "Answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " When were PopTarts invented?",
    "Answer": "1964"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In Norse mythology, how was called the icy underworld?",
    "Answer": "Niflheim"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which Roman god had two faces?",
    "Answer": "Janus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " After whom is the month of July named?",
    "Answer": "Julius Caesar"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In what Swiss city was the World Wide Web first developed?",
    "Answer": "Geneva"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What was the largest airplane ever built?",
    "Answer": "Spruce Goose"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What is the name of the largest building from ancient Rome that survives intact?",
    "Answer": "The Pantheon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " One of the 7 Wonders of the ancient world was a giant bronze statue, what was it called?",
    "Answer": "Colossus of Rhodes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Which holy book do not mention cats and rats?",
    "Answer": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the first living American to have his name appear on a postage stamp?",
    "Answer": "Charles Lindbergh"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What general's father was in charge of investigating the case of Charles Lindberg's kidnapped child?",
    "Answer": "Norman Schwarzkopf"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who surrendered on April 9, 1865, without Jefferson Davis' approval?",
    "Answer": "Robert E. Lee"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What general's estate did a vengeful Congress confiscate as the site for a cemetery?",
    "Answer": "Robert E. Lee"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What woman did Hitler hire to glamorize scenes in films such as 'Triumph of the Will'?",
    "Answer": "Leni Riefenstahl"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Whose 1923 death prompted Henry Cabot Lodge to gush: 'My God! That means Coolidge is president'?",
    "Answer": "Warren G. Harding's"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What section of Los Angeles did these National Guardsmen patrol during this 1965 riot?",
    "Answer": "Watts"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What commodity did Jay Gould and James Fisk corner here in 1869, sparking 'Black Friday'?",
    "Answer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What Native American currency was the first market commodity to be 'cornered,' in 1666?",
    "Answer": "Wampum"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What ship had lifeboat space for half of its passengers when it rammed an iceberg in 1912?",
    "Answer": "The 'Titanic'"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What did Nikita Khrushchev call the rocket NASA tried to launch two months after 'Sputnik' made history?",
    "Answer": "Kaputnik"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What navigators might never have found the Pacific Ocean without the help of a Native American?",
    "Answer": "Meriwether Lewis and William Clark"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What did Sir Galahad search for?",
    "Answer": "The Holy Grail"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year saw the break up of the USSR?",
    "Answer": "1991"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year did the Russian revolution take place?",
    "Answer": "1917"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the first person to set foot on the moon?",
    "Answer": "Neil Armstrong"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year was a sheep named Dolly created by cloning?",
    "Answer": "1997"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year did the Titanic sink?",
    "Answer": "1912"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What war first gave Americans Uncle Sam on a poster, saying 'I Want You'?",
    "Answer": "World War I"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What feisty feminist claimed at a 1992 rally that she was 'the mother of you all'?",
    "Answer": "Betty Friedan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What future president saw 22 of his slaves join British forces in the American Revolution?",
    "Answer": "Thomas Jefferson"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who noted: 'It will make a big bang - a very big bang - but it is not a weapon which is useful in war'?",
    "Answer": "J. Robert Oppenheimer"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What future South Dakota senator piloted a B-24 in 355 combat missions during World War II?",
    "Answer": "George McGovern"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What stoic British statesman smoked an estimated 300,000 stogies?",
    "Answer": "Winston Churchill"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What Soviet rose to power after V.I. Lenin's death in 1924?",
    "Answer": "Joseph Stalin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What Texas governor was wounded by a shot from the gun that killed John F. Kennedy?",
    "Answer": "John Connally"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What lawyer defended John Scopes, teacher of Charles Darwin's theory of evolution, in 1925?",
    "Answer": "Clarence Darrow"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What Shoshone woman was traded to a member of this expedition by her Mandan captors?",
    "Answer": "Sacajawea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who'd just stuck his neck into a gillotine when he yelled: 'May my blood cement the happiness of France'?",
    "Answer": "Louis XVI"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Whose last words while facing a firing squad on April 28, 1945, were: 'No ... No!'?",
    "Answer": "Benito Mussolini"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What U.S. Chief Justice chaired the commission to investigate John F. Kennedy's assassination?",
    "Answer": "Earl Warren"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What ship made the first navigational use of the new S.O.S. signal, on April 14, 1912?",
    "Answer": "Titanic"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What was the target of the worst terrorist attack on U.S. soil, in 1993?",
    "Answer": "The World Trade Center"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What was Billy the Kid's original first name?",
    "Answer": "Henry"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What boat gave its name to the 100 Guineas Cup after winning it in 1851?",
    "Answer": "America"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What city hosted the 1967 World's Fair that featured a geodesic dome?",
    "Answer": "Montreal"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What ancient Greek philosopher bit the dust after downing a drink infused with hemlock?",
    "Answer": "Socrates"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What member of Bill Clinton's administration first championed the information highway?",
    "Answer": "Al Gore"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Whose crew is blamed for introducing smallpox to America and syphilis to Europe?",
    "Answer": "Christopher Columbus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " Who was the first person in space?",
    "Answer": "Yuri Gagarin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " What year was the Commonwealth of Australia established?",
    "Answer": "1901"
  },
  {
    "Category": "History",
    "Question": " In Norse mythology, what was the Twilight of the Gods called?",
    "Answer": "Ragnarok"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Who wrote 'Chitty Chitty Bang Bang'?",
    "Answer": "Ian Fleming"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the true identity of 'Kay Challis'?",
    "Answer": "Crazy Jane"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the true identity of 'Maggie Sawyer'?",
    "Answer": "Maggie Sawyer"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the name of Captain Nemo's submarine?",
    "Answer": "Nautilus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the name of Dumas' 3 musketeers?",
    "Answer": "Porthos, Athos and Aramis"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the river named most often in the Bible?",
    "Answer": "Jordan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " In JRR Tolkien's Lord of the Rings, 3 wizards are mentioned by name: Gandalf, Saruman, and who?",
    "Answer": "Radagast"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " 'The Diary of Anne Frank' was first published in English under what title?",
    "Answer": "Diary of a Young Girl"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the name of the 4 Horsemen of the Apocalypse.",
    "Answer": "War, Pestilence, Famine and Death"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What famous British novel begins with the line: 'It was a cold day in April, and the clocks were striking thirteen'?",
    "Answer": "1984"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " According to Douglas Adams' 'Hitchhiker's Guide To The Galaxy', who designed Norway?",
    "Answer": "Slartibartfast"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote the novel, 'Jaws'?",
    "Answer": "Peter Benchley"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Illiad'?",
    "Answer": "Alexander Pope"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'The Silence of the Lambs'?",
    "Answer": "Thomas Harris"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'A Bridge to Far'?",
    "Answer": "Cornelius Ryan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'A Christmas Carol?",
    "Answer": "Charles Dickens"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'A Clockwork Orange?",
    "Answer": "Anthony Burgess"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'As I Lay Dying?",
    "Answer": "William Faulkner"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Cardinal of the Kremlin?",
    "Answer": "Tom Clancy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Catch 22?",
    "Answer": "Joseph Heller"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Cry the Beloved Country?",
    "Answer": "Alan Paton"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Deptford Trilogy?",
    "Answer": "Robertson Davies"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'El Gringo?",
    "Answer": "Carlos Fuentes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Fahrenheit 451?",
    "Answer": "Ray Bradbury"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Ice Palace?",
    "Answer": "Edna Furber"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Interview with a Vampire?",
    "Answer": "Anne Rice"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Ironweed?",
    "Answer": "William Kennedy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Islands in the Stream?",
    "Answer": "Ernest Hemingway"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Jane Eyre'?",
    "Answer": "Charlotte Bronte"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Lightning'?",
    "Answer": "Dean Koontz"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Little Country'?",
    "Answer": "Charles de Lint"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Lolita'?",
    "Answer": "Vladimir Nabokov"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Movable Feast'?",
    "Answer": "Ernest Hemingway"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Murders of Rue Morgue'?",
    "Answer": "Edgar Allan Poe"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Pilgrims Progress'?",
    "Answer": "John Bunyan"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Portnoy's Complaint'?",
    "Answer": "Philip Roth"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Puppet Masters'?",
    "Answer": "Robert Heinlein"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Silas Marner'?",
    "Answer": "George Elliot"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Single and Single'?",
    "Answer": "John le Carre"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Someplace to Be Flying'?",
    "Answer": "Charles de Lint"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Sound and the Fury'?",
    "Answer": "William Faulkner"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Sum of All Fears'?",
    "Answer": "Tom Clancy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'The Runaway Jury'?",
    "Answer": "John Grisham"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Travels'?",
    "Answer": "Marco Polo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Vet in Harness'?",
    "Answer": "James Herriot"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Wizard of Oz'?",
    "Answer": "Lyman Frank Baum"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Which author wrote 'Zorba the Greek'?",
    "Answer": "Nikos Kazantzakis"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": "In which novel by George Eliot is Eppie Cass adopted by a miser whose gold has been stolen by her father?",
    "Answer": "Silas Marner"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What poet immortalized a famous silversmith's midnight ride to warn that the British were coming?",
    "Answer": "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is a famous RAH novel, as well as a number believed to be cursed?",
    "Answer": "The number of the beast"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " According to the title of a famous novel, there are how many 'Years of Solitude'?",
    "Answer": "One hundred"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What was Odysseus' dog's name?",
    "Answer": "Argos"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Who or what was the only one to recognize Odysseus when he arrived home after an absence of 20 years?",
    "Answer": "His dog, Argos"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What famous ancient Greek author wrote about the epic journey of Odysseus?",
    "Answer": "Homer"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " Who said: 'Fie Fi Fo Fum, I smell the blood of an Englishman'?",
    "Answer": "The giant in 'Jack In The Beanstalk'"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Literatures",
    "Question": " What is the name of the antagonist in Peter Pan?",
    "Answer": "Captain Hook"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'A ___ to a Kill'.",
    "Answer": "View"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'A ___ to India'.",
    "Answer": "Passage"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Baby ___'.",
    "Answer": "Boom"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Big ___ in Little China'.",
    "Answer": "Trouble"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Black ___'.",
    "Answer": "Rain"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Dead ___ Don't Wear Plaid'.",
    "Answer": "Men"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Dirty ___'.",
    "Answer": "Dancing"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Driving Miss ___'.",
    "Answer": "Daisy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'First ___'.",
    "Answer": "Blood"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'For Your ___ Only'.",
    "Answer": "Eyes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Less than ___'.",
    "Answer": "Zero"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Mr. ___'.",
    "Answer": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'My Left ___'.",
    "Answer": "Foot"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ Eye'.",
    "Answer": "Cat's"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Say ___'.",
    "Answer": "Anything"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'The ___ Crystal'.",
    "Answer": "Dark"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ Guy'.",
    "Answer": "Lonely"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'The Right ___'.",
    "Answer": "Stuff"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'The ___ Brothers'.",
    "Answer": "Blues"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'This is ___ Tap'.",
    "Answer": "Spinal"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Three Men and a ___'.",
    "Answer": "Baby"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Urban ___'.",
    "Answer": "Cowboy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'War___'.",
    "Answer": "Games"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ Boys'.",
    "Answer": "Bad"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ By Me'.",
    "Answer": "Stand"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'The Evil ___'.",
    "Answer": "Dead"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'The Last ___ of Christ'.",
    "Answer": "Temptation"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Sex, Lies and ___'.",
    "Answer": "Videotape"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'Some Kind of ___'.",
    "Answer": "Wonderful"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'The Big ___'.",
    "Answer": "Chill"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ of Dreams'.",
    "Answer": "Field"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ of Fire'.",
    "Answer": "Chariots"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ of the Universe'.",
    "Answer": "Masters"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ of War'.",
    "Answer": "Casualties"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ Taste'.",
    "Answer": "Bad"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ That Girl?'.",
    "Answer": "Who's"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: '___ the 13th'.",
    "Answer": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the title of this 80s film: 'No Way ___'.",
    "Answer": "Out"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'In the Southeast, they say if you want to go to heaven, you have to change planes in Atlanta.'?",
    "Answer": "Accidental Tourist"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'Andy McCarthy does Robby Lowe's Mom, and she's Jackie Bissette!'?",
    "Answer": "Class"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'Bill Murray, post-SNL, pre-Groundhog. Think spaghetti.'?",
    "Answer": "Meatballs"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'Guy really gets into playing videogames.'?",
    "Answer": "Tron"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'Hmm. Let's make Chevy Chase a spy!'?",
    "Answer": "Fletch"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'Proof that there's life in the afterlife. And Geena Davis's lips.'?",
    "Answer": "Beetlejuice"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'Ricki Lake. Before her television show.'?",
    "Answer": "Hairspray"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'The bitch is back, and it's not Sigourney.'?",
    "Answer": "Aliens"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To which 80s film this quote came from: 'The paean to late nights and teens in the 1950s'?",
    "Answer": "Diner"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the movie 'Godzilla', what was the name of Godzilla's son?",
    "Answer": "Minya"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'The Wolfman', what was Lon Chaney Jr's human name?",
    "Answer": "Larry Talbot"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete this quote: 'Enter freely, of your own will, and leave some of the...'.",
    "Answer": "Happiness you bring"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Halloween', Michael Myers' mask was made from the novelty Halloween mask of what well-known actor?",
    "Answer": "William Shatner"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the 'Leprechaun' series, who played the title character?",
    "Answer": "Warwick Davis"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Who was the '50's horror film hostess that also appeared in 'Plan 9 from Outer Space'?",
    "Answer": "Vampira"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What was the only thing that Beetlejuice was afraid of?",
    "Answer": "Sand worms"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What was the name of the Addams Family butler?",
    "Answer": "Lurch"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Rosemary's Baby', which actress played the mother?",
    "Answer": "Mia Farrow"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'The Rocky Horror Picture Show', what was the name of the Faithful Handyman?",
    "Answer": "Riff Raff"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Which actor has played Dracula in more films than anyone else?",
    "Answer": "Christopher Lee"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete this quote: 'Soylent Green is...'.",
    "Answer": "People"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 1921's 'Nosferatu', what was the name of the villian?",
    "Answer": "Count Orlock"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " To what was Dracula referring to as 'children of the night'?",
    "Answer": "Wolves"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 1943's 'Son of Dracula', which actor played Count Alucard?",
    "Answer": "Lon Chaney Jr"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the 1931 film 'Frankenstein', what was the doctor's first name?",
    "Answer": "Henry"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'A Nightmare on Elm Street', how many blades were on Freddy Kruger's glove?",
    "Answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": "  In 'Interview with the Vampire', in what city does the interview take place?",
    "Answer": "San Fransisco"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the 1986 remake of 'The Fly', what was the name of the scientist that accidentally had his dna mixed with that of a fly?",
    "Answer": "Seth Brundle"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 1985's 'Teen Wolf', what television star played the title role?",
    "Answer": "Michael J. Fox"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Abbott and Costello meet Frankenstein', what character did Vincent Price play?",
    "Answer": "Invisible man"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'The Munsters', what was 'The Munsters''s street address?",
    "Answer": "1313 Mockingbird Lane"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Star Trek', what colour was Mr Spock's blood?",
    "Answer": "Green"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Love at First Bite', who played Dracula?",
    "Answer": "George Hamilton"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In Stephen King's 'IT', what was the name of the clown?",
    "Answer": "Pennywise"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Halloween H20', who played Jamie Lee Curtis' 'Psycho' mother?",
    "Answer": "Janet Leigh"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the 'The Evil Dead' trilogy, what was the name of the hero played by Bruce Campbell?",
    "Answer": "Ash"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Psycho', what was Norman Bates' hobby?",
    "Answer": "Taxidermy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete this quote from the monster in Frankenstein: 'Fire...'.",
    "Answer": "Bad!"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'From Dusk Til Dawn', the 'heroes' stumble into a nightclub full of what?",
    "Answer": "Vampires"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In Hammer's 'The Curse of Frankenstein', what role did Christopher Lee play?",
    "Answer": "Monster"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 1957's 'I was a Teenage Werewolf', which television star played the title role?",
    "Answer": "Michael Landon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 1925's 'The Phantom of the Opera', what was the title character's name?",
    "Answer": "Eric"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What was Bela Lugosi's real name?",
    "Answer": "Bela Blasko"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the 1986 remake of 'The Little Shop of Horrors', who played the masochistic dental patient?",
    "Answer": "Bill Murray"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What actress played in the movies 'Firestarter' and 'E.T.'?",
    "Answer": "Drew Barrymore"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'King Kong vs. Godzilla', who won?",
    "Answer": "Neither"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the film 'Them', the monsters were giant what?",
    "Answer": "Ants"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What type of bat is most often used in horror films?",
    "Answer": "Flying fox"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " On the original 'The Munsters' television series, who played Herman?",
    "Answer": "Fred Gwynne"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Beverly Hills Cop', when Axel Foley enters the hotel, for whom he claims to work?",
    "Answer": "Rolling Stone"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Beverly Hills Cop', when Axel Foley enters the hotel, who does he say he's going to interview?",
    "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " This citation are the last words of which film: 'Louis, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship'?",
    "Answer": "Casablanca"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What was the first 'James Bond' film?",
    "Answer": "Dr. No"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Which actor, born may 7, 1901, have starred in the movie 'Dallas'?",
    "Answer": "Gary Cooper"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " When actor Arnold Schwarzenegger bought the first Hummer manufactured for civilian use?",
    "Answer": "1992"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete the name of this actor :  '______ Borgnine'.",
    "Answer": "Ernest"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What movie had Michael Keaton playing a character loosely named after a huge star in the constellation of Orion?",
    "Answer": "Beetlejuice"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In the 'Omen' trilogy, what was the name of the antichrist character?",
    "Answer": "Damien"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Complete this quote: 'It's alive! ______'.",
    "Answer": "It's alive"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
	"Question": " 'The Shining' was the film playing at the drive-in in which film?",
    "Answer": "Twister"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'War of the Worlds', what finally destroyed the aliens?",
    "Answer": "Germs"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Nightmare on Elm Street', what young actor was eaten by a bed?",
    "Answer": "Johnny Depp"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'The Blair Witch Project', what was the town of Blair renamed as?",
    "Answer": "Burkittsville"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " 'Oliver's Story' was the sequel to which Erich Segal's best-seller?",
    "Answer": "Love story"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " 'Back in the Habit' is the sub-title to which film sequel?",
    "Answer": "Sister act 2"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " In 'Carrie', who played the title role?",
    "Answer": "Sissy Spacek"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " Who was billed as the 'Man of 1000 Faces'?",
    "Answer": "Lon Chaney"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " A character named 'Spearchucker Jones' was deleted from which famous American television show's cast after only five episodes?",
    "Answer": "MASH"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What Disney animated feature required the drawing of 6,469,952 black spots?",
    "Answer": "101 Dalmatians"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Movies",
    "Question": " What film puts an animated rodent to work, hauling buckets of water in his masters abode?",
    "Answer": "Fantasia"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": "To which female singer the number '39' is a reference?",
	"Answer": "Miku Hatsune"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " To which Dire Straits' music these lyrics came from: 'And the big wheel keep on turning neon burning up above'?",
    "Answer": "Tunnel of love"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " 'Bowser' and 'Jocko' have been two prominent members of what very successful rock & roll nostalgia act?",
    "Answer": "Sha Na Na"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " Who sang 'Never Say Never'?",
    "Answer": "Romeo Void"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": "Kiss on My List' was which duo's second number one hit?",
    "Answer": "Hall and Oates"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " What top-selling Christmas single of 1985 was not the least bit amusing to many senior citizens?",
    "Answer": "Grandma Got Run Over by a Reindeer"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " What cult leader was rejected at an audition for The Monkees for just not being cute enough?",
    "Answer": "Charles Manson"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " To which Dire Straits' music these lyrics came from: 'You get a shiver in the dark, it's raining in the park ...'?",
    "Answer": "Sultans of Swing"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " To which ZZ-Top's music these lyrics came from: 'The girls'll go crazy for a....'?",
    "Answer": "Sharp Dressed Man"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " 'Dr. Feelgood' was which group's last album with Vince Neill?",
    "Answer": "Motley Crue"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " How did Kurt Cobain announce The Meat Puppets on Nirvana's 'Unplugged in New York?",
    "Answer": "Thing 1 and Thing 2"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " What child star was the first person signed by MGM without having to take a screen or sound test?",
    "Answer": "Judy Garland"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " What was received on the second day of Christmas, according to the song?",
    "Answer": "Two turtledoves"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " Who were the guest artists in Nirvana's 'Unplugged in New York?",
    "Answer": "The Meat Puppets"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " Which east L.A kid had a memorable top ten hit about his girlfriend Donna?",
    "Answer": "Richie Valens"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Musics",
    "Question": " What English-language song is the most frequently sung?",
    "Answer": "Happy Birthday to You"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is the name of the 2 friends of Nadekobot?",
    "Answer": "RoboNitori and Bakabot"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is a word formed from the initials of other words?",
    "Answer": "Acronym"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'WYSIWYG'?",
    "Answer": "What you see is what you get"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'DWAI'?",
    "Answer": "Driving While Ability Impaired"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'JVC'?",
    "Answer": "Japan Victor Company"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'ACK'?",
    "Answer": "ACKnowledgement"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'ANSI'?",
    "Answer": "American National Standards Institute"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'AOL'?",
    "Answer": "America On Line"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'AWGTHTGTTA'?",
    "Answer": "Are We Going To Have To Go Through This/That Again"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BAC'?",
    "Answer": "By Any Chance"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BAK'?",
    "Answer": "Back At Keyboard"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BBL'?",
    "Answer": "Be Back Later"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BOS'?",
    "Answer": "Boyfriend Over Shoulder"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BRT'?",
    "Answer": "Be Right There"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BST'?",
    "Answer": "British Summer Time"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BTOBD'?",
    "Answer": "Be There Or Be Dead"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'BWL'?",
    "Answer": "Bursting With Laughter"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'COD'?",
    "Answer": "Cash On Delivery"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'DBN'?",
    "Answer": "Doing Business Not"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'DFM'?",
    "Answer": "Don't Flame Me"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'DIIK'?",
    "Answer": "Damned If I Know"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'DOB'?",
    "Answer": "Date Of Birth"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'DWIM'?",
    "Answer": "Do What I Mean"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'E2EG'?",
    "Answer": "Ear To Ear Grin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'EMSG'?",
    "Answer": "Email MeSsaGe"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'FIRST'?",
    "Answer": "Forum of Incident Response and Security Teams"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'FOAF'?",
    "Answer": "Friend Of A Friend"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'FOD'?",
    "Answer": "Finger Of Death"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'FURTB'?",
    "Answer": "Full Up Ready To Burst"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'GAFIA'?",
    "Answer": "Get Away From It All"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'GIWIST'?",
    "Answer": "Gee I Wish I'd Said That"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'GMT'?",
    "Answer": "Greenwich Mean Time"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'HTTP'?",
    "Answer": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'IAAD'?",
    "Answer": "I Am A Doctor"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'IAE'?",
    "Answer": "In Any Event"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'IBTD'?",
    "Answer": "I Beg To Differ"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'IMBO'?",
    "Answer": "In My Biased Opinion"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'IWALY'?",
    "Answer": "I Will Always Love You"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'JIC'?",
    "Answer": "Just In Case"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'JTLYK'?",
    "Answer": "Just To Let You Know"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'JTUSK'?",
    "Answer": "Just Thought You Should Know"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'JTYMLTK'?",
    "Answer": "Just Thought You Might Like To Know"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'L8TRZ'?",
    "Answer": "LATeRS"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'LHU'?",
    "Answer": "Lord Help Us"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'LLAP'?",
    "Answer": "Live Long And Prosper"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'LMC'?",
    "Answer": "Lost My Connection"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'LoTR'?",
    "Answer": "Lord of The Rings"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'LSFIAB'?",
    "Answer": "Like Shooting Fish In A Barrel"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'LYLAB'?",
    "Answer": "Love You Like A Brother"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'MD'?",
    "Answer": "MaileD"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'MHM'?",
    "Answer": "Members Helping Members"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'MHOTY'?",
    "Answer": "My Hat's Off To You"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'MIPS'?",
    "Answer": "Meaningless Information Per Second"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'MORF'?",
    "Answer": "Male OR Female"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'NAGI'?",
    "Answer": "Not A Good Idea"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'NDM'?",
    "Answer": "No Disrespect Meant"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'NIDWTC'?",
    "Answer": "No I Don't Want To Chat"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'NIH'?",
    "Answer": "Not Invented Here"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'NOOTO'?",
    "Answer": "Nothing Out Of The Ordinary"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'NYM'?",
    "Answer": "New York Minute"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'OTT'?",
    "Answer": "Over The Top"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'PAW'?",
    "Answer": "Parents Are Watching"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'PDQ'?",
    "Answer": "Pretty Damn Quick"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'PIMP'?",
    "Answer": "Pee In My Pants"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'PLMKO'?",
    "Answer": "Please Let Me Know Ok"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'PMBI'?",
    "Answer": "Pardon My Butting In"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'PTO'?",
    "Answer": "Please Turn Over"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'Q'?",
    "Answer": "Queue"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'QPQ'?",
    "Answer": "Quid Pro Quo"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'RA'?",
    "Answer": "Red Alert"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'ROFLMHO'?",
    "Answer": "Rolling On Floor Laughing My Head Off"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'ROTFLAS'?",
    "Answer": "Rolling On The Floor Laughing And Snorting"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'RTS'?",
    "Answer": "Real Time Strategy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'SASS'?",
    "Answer": "Short Attention Span Society/Syndrome"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'SMOFF'?",
    "Answer": "Serious Mode OFF"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'SMOP'?",
    "Answer": "Small Matter Of Programming"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'SNR'?",
    "Answer": "Signal to Noise Ratio"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'SOHB'?",
    "Answer": "Sense Of Humour Bypass"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'ST-DS9'?",
    "Answer": "Star Trek - Deep Space 9"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'SUFID'?",
    "Answer": "Screwing Up Face In Disgust"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'TBE'?",
    "Answer": "To Be Expected"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'TIATLG'?",
    "Answer": "Truly I Am The Living God"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'TMIKTLIU'?",
    "Answer": "The More I Know The Less I Understand"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'TN'?",
    "Answer": "TelNet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'TRDMC'?",
    "Answer": "Tears Running Down My Cheeks"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'UUCP'?",
    "Answer": "Unix-toUnix CoPy"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'VR'?",
    "Answer": "Virtual Reality"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'W/'?",
    "Answer": "With"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'WAIS'?",
    "Answer": "Wide Area Information Server"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'WC'?",
    "Answer": "Way Cool"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'WYM'?",
    "Answer": "What You Mean?"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'YCLIU'?",
    "Answer": "You Can Look It Up"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'YGTBK'?",
    "Answer": "You've Got To Be Kidding"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'YHBW'?",
    "Answer": "You Have Been Warned"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What mean this acronym: 'YKYATP'?",
    "Answer": "You Know You're A Tired Parent"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How a group of cattle is called?",
    "Answer": "Herd"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How a group of ducks is called?",
    "Answer": "Brace"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How a group of lion is called?",
    "Answer": "Pride"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " A hoop worn under skirts is called a what?",
    "Answer": "Farthingale"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " A kipper is what type of smoked fish?",
    "Answer": "Herring"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a large French country house?",
    "Answer": "Chateau"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a light canvas shoe with a plaited sole?",
    "Answer": "Espadrille"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " A magnum of champagne is how many litres?",
    "Answer": "1.5"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What a male singer whose sexual organs have been modified is known as?",
    "Answer": "Castrato"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a person refusing to join a strike?",
    "Answer": "Blackleg"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " A sadhu is a holy man in which country?",
    "Answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What name a sailor who has not yet crossed the equator is referred to?",
    "Answer": "Pollywog"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What a salad containing diced apple, celery, walnuts and mayonnaise is known as?",
    "Answer": "Waldorf salad"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a ships officer in charge of equipment and crew?",
    "Answer": "Boatswain"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What all Hebrew orignating names that end with the letters 'el' have something to do with?",
    "Answer": "God"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " In kilograms, how much does one litre of water weigh?",
    "Answer": "1 Kg"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a short legged hunting dog?",
    "Answer": "Basset"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is the meaning of the French word 'estragon'?",
    "Answer": "Tarragon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What does the ancient Greek word 'electron' mean?",
    "Answer": "Amber"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What African language do Boers speak?",
    "Answer": "Afrikaans"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What does the Russian word 'Buran' mean?",
    "Answer": "Blizzard"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is a Wyvern?",
    "Answer": "A type of dragon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a short womens jacket without fastenings?",
    "Answer": "Bolero"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a small crown?",
    "Answer": "Coronet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": "100 zeros after the number 1 is a very very large number called what?",
    "Answer": "Googol"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is the Scottish word for 'Lake'?",
    "Answer": "Loch"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " According to superstition, what do you do when you stub the toes on your right foot?",
    "Answer": "Make a wish"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
	"Question": " '7x' was used to refer to the secret ingredient of what drink?",
    "Answer": "Coca Cola"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How many cars does the average Kuwaiti driver have registered?",
    "Answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What do some stock market wizards call a '007'?",
    "Answer": "A bond"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " The 1st January of what year have marked the first day of the 21st century?",
    "Answer": "2001"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " Which product is more money spent on per year, baby food or pet food?",
    "Answer": "Pet food"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What do American parents of infants dump 17 billion of each year?",
    "Answer": "Disposable diapers"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is the world's most widely spoken language?",
    "Answer": "The Mandarin dialect of Chinese"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " True or false: The word 'karate' means 'empty hand'.",
    "Answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " If offered a new pen to write with, what will 97% of people do with it?",
    "Answer": "Write their own name"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called a small pickled cucumber?",
    "Answer": "gherkin"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " According to U.S. law, what may not be granted on a useless invention?",
    "Answer": "Patent"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " Most people wear a watch on their left or right wrist?",
    "Answer": "Left"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What profession is troubled by the most workplace violence?",
    "Answer": "Police officers"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What are the 3 best-known western personages in China?",
    "Answer": "Jesus Christ, Richard Nixon and Elvis Presley"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": "In Greek language, what mean 'polis'?",
    "Answer": "City"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What do you study if you are studying entomology?",
    "Answer": "Insects"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What is the official language of Egypt?",
    "Answer": "Arabic"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " If you study etymology, what are you studying?",
    "Answer": "Word origins"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " Complete this slogan : 'Always _______'.",
    "Answer": "Coca Cola"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called an addition to a will?",
    "Answer": "Codicil"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called the study of religion?",
    "Answer": "Theology"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called the study of mans and their culture?",
    "Answer": "Anthropology"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called an area seperating potential belligerents?",
    "Answer": "Buffer zone"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is called an underground layer of water filled rock?",
    "Answer": "Aquifer"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": "How is called an advertising film which is informative and purportedly objective?",
    "Answer": "Infomercial"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What autonomous region would the Dalai Lama like to call home?",
    "Answer": "Tibet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " What fixture in the White House was called a 'Quincy'?",
    "Answer": "The toilet"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Other",
    "Question": " How is also called guardian angels?",
    "Answer": "Watchers"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Define the value of X: '-10x - 19 = 19 - 8x'.",
    "Answer": "-19"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Define the value of X: '99 + 5x = 2000 - 5x - 911'.",
    "Answer": "99"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is the square root of '-1'?",
    "Answer": "i"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " A capital 'D' is the Roman numeral for which number?",
    "Answer": "Five hundred"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How many seconds a day have?",
    "Answer": "86400"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": "What is the acronym for 'quasi-stellar radio source'?",
    "Answer": "Quasar"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is actually caused by layers of hot air refracting sunlight?",
    "Answer": "Mirage"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What invention did the most to discourage the practice of letter writing?",
    "Answer": "The telephone"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What country was proud to see Marc Garneau as it's first astronaut 1984?",
    "Answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What rock floats in water?",
    "Answer": "Pumice"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How is called an anti-tank rocket launcher?",
    "Answer": "Bazooka"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What type of engineering sees organisms have their DNA altered to produce new substances?",
    "Answer": "Genetic engineering"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How is commonly called phencyclidine hydrochloride?",
    "Answer": "Angel dust"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What letter does the first four notes of Beethoven's Fifth Symphony denote in Morse code?",
    "Answer": "V"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What was the first transatlantic radio message sent?",
    "Answer": "S"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Which artificial fiber was invented in 1938?",
    "Answer": "Nylon"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How is scientifically called wood alcohol?",
    "Answer": "Methanol"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What Intel chip is the successor to the 80286, 80386 and 80486?",
    "Answer": "Pentium"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is the type of computer virus that is named after a device of trickery used in a famous mythological war?",
    "Answer": "Trojan Horse"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " When was the World Wide Web developed?",
    "Answer": "1990"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is the name of the group that developed the World Wide Web?",
    "Answer": "European Center for Nuclear Research"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is the most abundant metal in the Earth's crust?",
    "Answer": "Aluminum"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What substance is the largest single preventable cause of death?",
    "Answer": "Tobacco"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What number is indicated by this symbol in the Greek numeral system 'VII'?",
    "Answer": "Seven"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What's the term for a device that uses the sun and horizon to determine location?",
    "Answer": "Sextant"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What planet did the U.S. 'Viking I' send surface images of, starting in 1976?",
    "Answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What invention rendered the short-lived Pony Express delivery service unnecessary?",
    "Answer": "The telegraph"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " The sun sets in what cardinal direction?",
    "Answer": "West"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Which planet is closest to the sun?",
    "Answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How many moons does Mars have?",
    "Answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What tracking device was the Stealth bomber designed to evade?",
    "Answer": "Radar"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What's the heaviest naturally-occurring element?",
    "Answer": "Uranium"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What does a speleologist study?",
    "Answer": "Caves"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Which of the 9 planets in our solar system is blue and white when seen from outer space?",
    "Answer": "Earth"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What oceanic climatic condition is named after the Spanish term for 'the Christ Child'?",
    "Answer": "El Nino"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What's the most abundant element on earth?",
    "Answer": "Oxygen"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What's the astronomical phenomenon where the moon partially covers the sun called?",
    "Answer": "An eclipse"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How many natural satellites does Earth have?",
    "Answer": "One"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " 'Dephlogisticated air' was the name given by Joseph Priestley to which gas?",
    "Answer": "Oxygen"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " A 'double sheet bend' is a type of what?",
    "Answer": "Knot"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How a block of compressed coal dust used as fuel is called?",
    "Answer": "Briquette"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Air is 21% oxygen and 1% of other gases. What gaz is present at 78%?",
    "Answer": "Nitrogen"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is the name given to the change in pitch accompanied by an approaching or receeding sound source?",
    "Answer": "Doppler Effect"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How is called the classical medical symbol of two serpents wrapped around a staff?",
    "Answer": "Caduceus"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What are Pyxis, Puppis, and Pavo?",
    "Answer": "Constellations in the southern sky"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Which element makes up 2.83% of the Earth's crust?",
    "Answer": "Sodium"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Which element makes up 5% of the Earth's crust?",
    "Answer": "Iron"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What is a boat or raft with two parallel hulls?",
    "Answer": "Catamaran"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Does Uranus have an aurora?",
    "Answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " What cluster of stars is also known as the Seven Sisters?",
    "Answer": "Pleiades"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " Who invented the computer mouse?",
    "Answer": "Douglas C. Engelbart"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Science",
    "Question": " How is called a group of stars?",
    "Answer": "Constellation"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " In Basketball, who was a very tall center and a real ladies man?",
    "Answer": "Wilt the Stilt"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " How may percent of professional boxers have suffered brain damage: 10, 30, 50 or 90 percent?",
    "Answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " How many gold medals did Jesse Owens win in the 1936 Berlin Olympics?",
    "Answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " What kind of sportsman is endangered by 'nitrogen narcosis' at a depth of more than 130 feet?",
    "Answer": "Scuba diver"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " Who fought in the boxing match called 'The Thrilla in Manila'?",
    "Answer": "Muhammad Ali and Joe Frazier"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " What did Chicago Cubs owner Phil Wrigley say, in 1935, was 'just a fad, a passing fancy'?",
    "Answer": "Night baseball"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " Whose 565-foot home run over the wall at Griffith Stadium gave birth to the term 'tape measure shot'?",
    "Answer": "Mickey Mantle"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " What U.S. president asked for rules changes after 18 players died during the 1905 football season?",
    "Answer": "Theodore Roosevelt"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " What Olympic skater worked off her community service sentence serving meals to Oregon's elderly?",
    "Answer": "Tonya Harding"
  },
  {
    "Category": "Sports",
    "Question": " What did the press call Wilt Chamberlain, although he preferred to be called 'The Big Dipper'?",
    "Answer": "Wilt the Stilt"
  }
]
Status API Training Shop Blog About
© 2016 GitHub, Inc. Terms Privacy Security Contact Help
